Guide to the Yale Events and Activities Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs of Mike Marsland, university photographer, documenting Yale University, 1977-2003; Accession 2009-A-070
  - Ferraro, Geraldine Visit, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - Film Study Center [mm 258], 1995 January 17 (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - First Year Building Project [mm 204], 1994 June 20 (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - First Year Design Project [mm 298], 1995 April 25 (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - Building Project 1st Year Architecture Students, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - First Year Design Project [mm 383], 1996 April 29 (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - First Year Design Project [mm 459], 1997 April 28 (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - First Year Design Projects [mm 155], 1994 April 25 (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - Architecture Design Winners 1st year students: YBC, 1999 May 17-31 (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - Flint, Larry: Visit to Yale, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - FOCUS Program [mm 324], 1995 August 31 (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - FOCUS Program [mm 39], 1993 August 26 (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - FOCUS Program [mm 405], 1996 August 23-29 (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - Forestry: Horizon solutions [JB 23], 1992 May (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - Fox Gift to Yale Center for International and Area Studies (YCIAS) [mm 43], 1993 October 22 (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - Frank, Roberta (Portrait), Circa 1990s (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - Franklin, Benjamin, Circa 1990s (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - Fraternity Fundraiser [mm 350], 1995 October (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - "Free Bobby" @ Ingalls, Circa 1990s (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - Freshman Assembly and Reception, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - Freshman Class of 2002 Arrival, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - Freshman 2001 Arrival [mm 483], 1997 August 29 (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - Freshman Arrival 2000 [mm 406], 1996 August 30 (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - Freshman Arrival (class of 1999) [mm 329], 1995 (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - Freshman Arrival Class of 1997 [mm 40], 1993 August 27 (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - Freshman Arrival Class of 1996 [mm 7], 1992 August 28 (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - Freshman Arrival Class of 1995 [DD], 1991 August (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - Thomas Friedman Lecture [mm 512], 1998 February (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - Future Freshmen [mm 161], 1994 April (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - Future Freshman Days [mm 295], 1995 April 17 (Box 3, Folder 236)
  - Gelatin Wrestling: Masters of Pierson College (PC) and Jonathan Edwards (JE) College: YBC, 1999 May 3-17 (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - Gender Matters, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - Gergen, David [mm 506], 1998 February 20 (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - Gibbs, Josiah Willard, Circa 1990s (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - Gilder Lehrman Center Dedication Ceremony, 1998 November (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - Betsy Golden/Yale Band [MTM], 2001 (Box 3, Folder 242)
  - Jane Goodall -- Albert Schweitzer Lecturer [mm 121], 1993 April 2 (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - Goodwin, Doris Kearns: Gary Fryer Memorial Lecture (YBC 3/29/99), 1999 (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - Gordon Grand Fellowship -- John Sculley [Drew Dole 241], 1989 April 28 (Box 3, Folder 245)
  - Tipper Gore Visit [mm 204], 1994 April 5 (Box 3, Folder 246)
  - Graduate and Professional Assembly [mm 10], 1992 September 8 (Box 3, Folder 247)
  - Graduate and Professional Schools Assembly [mm 46], 1993 September 9 (Box 3, Folder 248)
  - Graduate School Psychology Alumni [mm 731], 1993 April 30 (Box 3, Folder 249)
  - Graduate School Newsletter Folder #2, Circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 250)
  - Graduate School Housing [mm 317], 1995 January (Box 4, Folder 251)
  - Graduate School: Centennial Celebration of Women's Ph.D.'s, 1992 April 24 (Box 4, Folder 252)
  - Graduates featured: Bockstoce, John, YBC, 1999 May 31 - June 21 (Box 4, Folder 253)
  - Green Guide presentation, 2000 June 21 (Box 4, Folder 254)
  - Grove Street Cemetary Celebration [mm 485], 1997 October 19 (Box 4, Folder 255)
  - Gymnastics [MTM], 2001 (Box 4, Folder 256)
  - Habitat for Humanity First Year Building Project [mm 70], 1993 April 27 (Box 4, Folder 257)
  - Habitat for Humanity [mm 307], 1995 April (Box 4, Folder 258)
  - Habitat for Humanity [mm 477], 1997 October 7 (Box 4, Folder 259)
  - Habitat for Humanity, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 260)
  - Halloween Parade [mm 482], 1997 October 29 (Box 4, Folder 261)
  - Halloween Party (President's House) [mm 347], 1995 October 31 (Box 4, Folder 262)
  - Halloween Parade (New Haven) [mm 343], 1995 October 27 (Box 4, Folder 263)
  - Koichi Hamada, Professor of Economics [mm 112], 1993 April 26 (Box 4, Folder 264)
  - "Handsome Dan" at Commencement, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 265)
  - Mascot: Handsome Dan ("Maurice"), 1992 May (Box 4, Folder 266)
  - Mascot: Handsome Dan, Circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 267)
  - Harkness carvings, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 268)
  - Jack Hasagawa Retirement Reception [mm 52], 1993 October 29 (Box 4, Folder 269)
  - Health Plan [mm 436], 1996 November (Box 4, Folder 270)
  - Health Service Department, Circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 271)
  - Heany, Seamus: Master's tea, 2000 October (Box 4, Folder 272)
  - Helicopter Lift -- Kline Biology Tower (KBT) Renovations [346 H Shapiro], 1995 November 5 (Box 4, Folder 273)
  - High School in the Community [mm 438], 1997 February 19 (Box 4, Folder 274)
  - Hill Development Project News Conference [mm 484], 1997 October 24 (Box 4, Folder 275)
  - Historic Preservation, Brochure Buildings, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 276)
  - Holiday Gifts [mm 251], 1994 November 29 (Box 4, Folder 277)
  - Holiday Gift Ideas [mm 471], 1996 November (Box 4, Folder 278)
  - Homebuyer Program
    - "400th homebuyer", Circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 279)
    - Participants, Circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 280)
    - Press Conference [mm 497], 1997 December 4 (Box 4, Folder 281)
    - Homebuyers Party [mm 301], 1995 May 4 (Box 4, Folder 282)
    - Homebuyers Project [mm 348], 1995 October 21 (Box 4, Folder 283)
    - Homebuyers Project [mm 154], 1994 May 11 (Box 4, Folder 284)
  - Hopper, Dennis (actor) Master's Tea, 1999 April 8 (Box 4, Folder 285)
  - Roger Horchow [mm 351], 1995 November 9 (Box 4, Folder 286)
  - Housing Tour -- "City Tour" [Harold Shapiro 257], 1994 October 29 (Box 4, Folder 287)
  - Housing + Urban Development (Cisneros) [mm 331], 1995 September 14 (Box 4, Folder 288)
  - Hsing- AY HSU (Music Award, RCL), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 289)
  - Huang, Cindy: Yale College Class of 1999, Circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 290)
  - IBYCUS [mm 3], 1992 September 23 (Box 4, Folder 291)
  - Ice Sculptures [mm 259], 1994 December (Box 4, Folder 292)
  - Insects (Peabody's Collection), 2001 September (Box 4, Folder 293)
  - Installation of University Chaplain [mm 9], 1992 October 4 (Box 4, Folder 294)
  - International Arts Festival, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 295)
  - International Festival of Arts and Ideas [mm 404], 1996 June 23-30 (Box 4, Folder 296)
  - International Festival of Arts and Ideas: YBC, 2001 June (Box 4, Folder 297)
  - Investments Brochure [mm 348], 1995 October (Box 4, Folder 298)
  - Investments Report [mm 437], 1996 December (Box 4, Folder 299)
  - ISPS Journal, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 300)
  - Jewish Community Center Press Conference [mm 448], 1996 December 20 (Box 4, Folder 301)
  - Junior Statesman Program [mm 219], 1994 July 28 (Box 4, Folder 302)
  - Kensington Street Project [mm 334], 1995 September 13 (Box 4, Folder 303)
  - Russ Konns: Weatherman [mm 85], 1994 February 11 (Box 4, Folder 304)
  - Lab shots [mm 470], 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 305)
  - Labyrinth Walk on Old Campus: YBC, 1999 May 17-31 (Box 4, Folder 306)
  - Lamar
    - Baseball Reception [mm 26], 1992 September (Box 4, Folder 307)
    - Western History Association [mm 17], 1992 October 16 (Box 4, Folder 308)
  - Lanman Wright Hall Dedication [mm 38], 1993 September 15 (Box 4, Folder 309)
  - Lapham Field Groundbreaking [mm1], 1992 December 7 (Box 4, Folder 310)
  - Lead-Safe House [mm 326], 1995 July 18 (Box 4, Folder 311)
  - LEAP (Leadership, Education and Athletics in Partnership) Program
    - [mm 390], 1996 October (Box 4, Folder 312)
    - [mm 211], 1994 July 14 (Box 4, Folder 313)
    - [mm 466], 1997 September (Box 4, Folder 314)
  - LEAP (Community Relations) [mm 22], 1992 November 19 (Box 4, Folder 315)
  - Lee, Annette: artist Open Studios (YBC), 1999 May 17-31 (Box 4, Folder 316)
  - Lee, Dr. Henry [mm 415], 1996 April 16 (Box 4, Folder 317)
  - Roger Lee: Undergrad Entrepreneur [mm 86], 1994 March (Box 4, Folder 318)
  - Lesbian and Gay Studies (Judith Halberstom/Edward Stein photos), 1996 September (Box 4, Folder 319)
  - Liebermen, Senator Joseph: Chubb Fellow, 1999 February 18 (Box 4, Folder 320)
  - Lincoln Painting at Yale Rep. [mm 77], 1994 January (Box 4, Folder 321)
  - Long Service Award Elizabeth Ford, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 322)
  - Long Service Awards Human Resources, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 323)
  - Long Service Award, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 324)
  - Long Service Awards [mm 399], 1996 May (Box 4, Folder 325)
  - Long Service Employees [mm 382], 1996 May (Box 4, Folder 326)
  - Long Service Employees, 2000 June (Box 4, Folder 327)
  - Lord's Cafeteria Reopening [mm 30], 1993 August 31 (Box 4, Folder 328)
  - Henry R. Luce Hall Groundbreaking [mm 72], 1993 March 11 (Box 4, Folder 329)
  - Magic Bus [mm 278], 1994 September 19 (Box 4, Folder 330)
  - Mambo Dance Lesson [mm 500], 1998 January (Box 4, Folder 331)
  - John Malone, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 332)
  - Management Training Institute [mm 389], 1996 June 5 (Box 4, Folder 333)
  - Management Training Seminar, 1999 October (Box 4, Folder 334)
  - Maple Cottage, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 335)
  - Mark MacCormack Master's Tea, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 336)
  - Marquand Chapel Steeple [mm 511], 1998 March (Box 4, Folder 337)
  - Marshall + Rhodes Scholars [mm 249], 1995 January 11 (Box 4, Folder 338)
  - Martin Luther King Day -- Ossie Davis [mm 458], 1997 January 20 (Box 4, Folder 339)
  - Martin, Sam: Presentation at Beinecke Library [Joy Bush], 1994 August (Box 4, Folder 340)
  - Massage Therapist [mm 424], 1996 October 11 (Box 4, Folder 341)
  - Master's in Journalism [mm 246], 1994 September 13 (Box 4, Folder 342)
  - Masters Tea with Shawn Colvin, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 343)
  - Masters' Tea: Calhoun College, Bruce Mathiske, 1998 December 4 (Box 4, Folder 344)
  - McCabe Reunion [mm 276], 1994 September 15 (Box 4, Folder 345)
  - McCourt, Frank Visit (author), 2000 December 4 (Box 4, Folder 346)
  - McCurry, Mike: White House Spokesman Campus Visit, 1999 February 2 (Box 4, Folder 347)
  - McDormand, Frances (Master's Tea Ezra Stiles), 2000 November 2 (Box 4, Folder 348)
  - McDougal Center [hs 481], 1997 October 24 (Box 4, Folder 349)
  - McDougal Center (Cafe) [mm 505], 1998 February 23 (Box 4, Folder 350)
  - Mechanical Engineering: Space Shuttle Project [mm 140], 1992 June 25 (Box 5, Folder 351)
  - Medical conference at BAC [MTM], 2008 March (Box 5, Folder 352)
  - Microsoft Corporation Visit [mm 15], 1992 December 8 (Box 5, Folder 353)
  - Michael Milinkovitch -- whale research [mm 127], 1993 January 11 (Box 5, Folder 354)
  - Microscope Exhibit: Medical School [MTM], 2001 (Box 5, Folder 355)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream [mm 5/10], 1998 March (Box 5, Folder 356)
  - MIF Meeting [mm 451], 1996 November 21 (Box 5, Folder 357)
  - Glen Miller Band, Circa 1990s (Box 5, Folder 358)
  - M+M- (blue) [mm 312], 1995 April 19 (Box 5, Folder 359)
  - "Modern Head" Sculpture [mm 284], 1994 May 22 (Box 5, Folder 360)
  - Don Moffitt -- Wall Street Journal (WSJ) [mm 248], 1994 November 14 (Box 5, Folder 361)
  - Multi-sports camp: Summer [mm 212], 1994 July 8 (Box 5, Folder 362)
  - "Mump and Smoot", Circa 1990s (Box 5, Folder 363)
  - Museum gift ideas [mm 60], 1993 November 29 (Box 5, Folder 364)
  - Museum Shops [mm 25], 1992 November 24 (Box 5, Folder 365)
  - Music Library Construction [mm 464.1], 1998 October (Box 5, Folder 366)
  - Music Library Dedication, 1998 October (Box 5, Folder 367)
  - MUSIC: Opera- "The Marriage of Figaro" (rehearsal) [mm 133], 1993 March 31 (Box 5, Folder 368)
  - Music, School of, and Cooperative High School, 1999 February-March (Box 5, Folder 369)
  - Music, School of: Staff/Faculty Unidentified, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 370)
  - MUSIC: Yale Opera [mm 97], 1994 April 7 (Box 5, Folder 371)
  - Music Box Collection [mm 71], 1993 November 18 (Box 5, Folder 372)
  - Music, School of/ Cooperative High School: Mike Seeger Guitar Class., Circa 1990s (Box 5, Folder 373)
  - MUSIC: Opera- "Burning Bright" (rehearsal) [mm 61], 1993 October 14 (Box 5, Folder 374)
  - Arthur Miller, playwright (YBC 12.7-14.98), 1998 (Box 5, Folder 375)
  - Nadar, Ralph (Yale Political Union) [mm 423], 1996 October 4 (Box 5, Folder 376)
  - National Youth Sports Program [mm 486], 1997 August 6 (Box 5, Folder 377)
  - NYSP at Yale: National Youth Sports Program, 2008 July (Box 5, Folder 378)
  - Nathan Hale [mm 502], 1997 November 8 (Box 5, Folder 379)
  - New Haven Art Space, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 380)
  - New Haven 101 [mm 337], 1995 September 9 (Box 5, Folder 381)
  - New Haven 101 [mm 412], 1996 September 7 (Box 5, Folder 382)
  - "New Haven 101" [mm 280], 1994 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 383)
  - New Haven Businesses [mm 319], 1995 April 11 (Box 5, Folder 384)
  - New Haven (corner Chape and College Street), Circa 1990s (Box 5, Folder 385)
  - New Haven community -- miscellaneous photos, Circa 1990s (Box 5, Folder 386)
  - New Haven First Tour [BS 393], 1996 July 11 (Box 5, Folder 387)
  - New Haven Urban Change [mm 328], 1995 August 22 (Box 5, Folder 388)
  - New Haven Initiative [mm 156], 1994 April 20 (Box 5, Folder 389)
  - New Haven Merchants, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 390)
  - New Haven Yale students (for New Haven Register), 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 391)
  - NIDA (National Institute on Drug Abuse)Conference, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 392)
  - Norton, Ed: visit to campus, 1999 October (Box 5, Folder 393)
  - Nota Bene: Winter [mm 82], 1994 February 10 (Box 5, Folder 394)
  - School of Nursing [mm 338], 1995 September 25 (Box 5, Folder 395)
  - Omni Hotel Announcement [mm 401], 1996 August 7 (Box 5, Folder 396)
  - Opera Publicity Shot: School of Music, Circa 1990s (Box 5, Folder 397)
  - Organs [mm 394], 1996 August 14 (Box 5, Folder 398)
  - Pacino, Al (Visit to campus), 1999 (Box 5, Folder 399)
  - Camille Paglia, Circa 1990s (Box 5, Folder 400)
  - Painting at the home of Robert Mnuchin [mm 113], 1993 February (Box 5, Folder 401)
  - Pataki, George: Governor of New York, Circa 1990s (Box 5, Folder 402)
  - Payne Whitney Gym
    - Fitness Center, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 403)
    - Swimming [mm 100], 1992 August 4 (Box 5, Folder 404)
    - Symphony painting project [mm 64], 1994 January (Box 5, Folder 405)
    - interior [mm 223], 1993 December 3 (Box 5, Folder 406)
    - Equipment [mm 335], 1995 September 18 (Box 5, Folder 407)
    - exteriors and interiors [mm 107], 1993 May 11 (Box 5, Folder 408)
  - "Path of Stars"- Ninth Square [mm 236], 1994 September 28 (Box 5, Folder 409)
  - Peabody Museum Mural [mm 464], 1997 September 10 (Box 5, Folder 410)
  - Peabody Museum -- "Dinosaur Visions" Exhibit Installation [mm 128], 1993 June 21 (Box 5, Folder 411)
  - Peace Games [mm 370], 1996 March 31 (Box 5, Folder 412)
  - Peace Games [mm 291], 1995 April 1 (Box 5, Folder 413)
  - Pediatric Specialty Center [mm 371], 1996 March 19 (Box 5, Folder 414)
  - Pepin, Jacques: Chef; YBC, 1999 May 31- June 21 (Box 5, Folder 415)
  - Pepper, John, Circa 1990s (Box 5, Folder 416)
  - Shimon Peres: Battell Chapel [mm 90], 1994 February 4 (Box 5, Folder 417)
  - Perot, Ross (Yale Political Union) [mm 422], 1996 January (Box 5, Folder 418)
  - Pew Grant [mm 339], 1995 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 419)
  - Physical Plant Employee [mm 157], 1994 May 24 (Box 5, Folder 420)
  - Physics Olympics [mm 466.1], Fall 1998 (Box 5, Folder 421)
  - Planned Giving Ad [mm 83], 1994 February 15 (Box 5, Folder 422)
  - Plisetkaya, Maya: Ballerina (YBC), 2001 September 28 (Box 5, Folder 423)
  - Police Hate Crime Program [mm 432], 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 424)
  - Police -- Yale, New Haven [mm 281], 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 425)
  - Police, University: Justice Dept Grant for Computers, 1999 January 25-February 1 (Box 5, Folder 426)
  - Political Union Lecture -- Robert Shapiro [mm 343], 1995 December (Box 5, Folder 427)
  - Porter Prize [mm 327], 1995 September (Box 5, Folder 428)
  - Pow Wow, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 429)
  - Power Lines -- Health risks [mm 94], 1994 April 8 (Box 5, Folder 430)
  - Power Plant [mm 507], 1998 February (Box 5, Folder 431)
  - Anthony Lewis at master's tea (Poynter Fellowship) [mm 98], 1994 March 29 (Box 5, Folder 432)
  - Poynter Fellowship
    - Howell Raines [mm 363], 1995 November (Box 5, Folder 433)
    - Tim Russert [mm 364], 1995 September 27 (Box 5, Folder 434)
    - Juan Williams [mm 418], 1996 November 13 (Box 5, Folder 435)
    - Greenfield [mm 503], 1998 February 4 (Box 5, Folder 436)
    - David Gergen [mm 290], 1995 March 23 (Box 5, Folder 437)
    - Bob Woodward [mm 230], 1994 October 5 (Box 5, Folder 438)
    - Hunter-Gault [mm 261], 1994 December (Box 5, Folder 439)
    - Frank Rich [mm 469.1], 1998 (Box 5, Folder 440)
  - Sister Helen Prejean [mm 498], 1997 October 15 (Box 5, Folder 441)
  - Presidents Reagon, Nixon, Bush and Ford, Circa 1990s (Box 6, Folder 442)
  - President's House/ Provost's House, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 443)
  - Presidents Breakfast Series [mm 283], 1995 March 22 (Box 6, Folder 444)
  - Presidential Fellow, 1997? (Box 6, Folder 445)
  - Presidential Service Fellows, 2000 July (Box 6, Folder 446)
  - Presidential Public Service Fellow [mm 217], 1994 August 12 (Box 6, Folder 447)
  - Prince School, New Haven: Nursing School Program, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 448)
  - Princess Victoria of Sweden, Circa 1990s (Box 6, Folder 449)
  - Private Industry Council (Community Relations) [mm 20], 1993 July 8 (Box 6, Folder 450)
  - Private Industry Council [mm 203], 1994 July 5 (Box 6, Folder 451)
  - Private Industry Council [mm 395], 1996 August 9 (Box 6, Folder 452)
  - Project X [mm 408], 1997 January 23 (Box 6, Folder 453)
  - Prosek, James, 1994 November (Box 6, Folder 454)
  - Publications Committee Meeting [mm 232], 1994 September 19 (Box 6, Folder 455)
  - Purchasing Department [mm 366], 1995 April 26 (Box 6, Folder 456)
  - Quilting [mm 467], 1997 September (Box 6, Folder 457)
  - Raines, Howell, Circa 1990s (Box 6, Folder 458)
  - Read Aloud Day [mm 293], 1995 April 25 (Box 6, Folder 459)
  - Recycling Department Campus Earth Summit [mm 76], 1994 January 27 (Box 6, Folder 460)
  - Recycling Program [mm 417], 1997 January 22 (Box 6, Folder 461)
  - Red Cross Blood Drive [mm 31], 1993 July (Box 6, Folder 462)
  - Red Cross -- Group shot in Yale Health Center [mm 123], 1993 June 15 (Box 6, Folder 463)
  - Reich, Charles at Law School, Circa 1990s (Box 6, Folder 464)
  - Renaissance Fellows, Community, 1997 Spring (Box 6, Folder 465)
  - Renovations
    - [mm 472], 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 466)
    - [mm 463.1], 1998 October (Box 6, Folder 467)
    - [mm 411], 1998 September (Box 6, Folder 468)
    - [mm 330], 1995 September (Box 6, Folder 469)
    - On Campus [mm 227], 1994 July (Box 6, Folder 470)
    - Sterling Memorial Library (SML), Lanman-Wright, Branford [mm 66], 1993 August 18 (Box 6, Folder 471)
  - [mm 229], 1992 October 5 (Box 6, Folder 472)
  - Rhodes and Marshall Scholarship Winners (YBC), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 473)
  - Rhodes Scholar [mm 104], 1992 December 8 (Box 6, Folder 474)
  - Rhodes Scholar -- Glenn Janes [mm 357], 1996 January 30 (Box 6, Folder 475)
  - Rhodes Marshall Scholars [mm 425], 1996 December 16 (Box 6, Folder 476)
  - Rideworks -- Commuting Program Union Station with Mayor [mm 51], 1993 October 28 (Box 6, Folder 477)
  - "RIF" Reading is Fundamental, 2000 February 10 (Box 6, Folder 478)
  - Riley, Richard US Sec'y of Education campus visit, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 479)
  - Ireland President, Mary Robinson [mm 340], 1995 October 16 (Box 6, Folder 480)
  - Robinson, Rachel [mm 447], 1997 April 9 (Box 6, Folder 481)
  - Robot Competition [mm 426], 1996 December (Box 6, Folder 482)
  - Robot Wars, 2000 April (Box 6, Folder 483)
  - Sidney Rogers [mm 92], 1994 April 4 (Box 6, Folder 484)
  - Rolling Stone Chuck Leavell, Forestry School, 1999 May 17-31 (Box 6, Folder 485)
  - Rollins Exhibit [mm 53], 1993 November (Box 6, Folder 486)
  - Rose Walk Dedication [mm 37], 1993 September 24 (Box 6, Folder 487)
  - Governor Pedro Rosello -- Puerto Rico [mm 359], 1996 January 29 (Box 6, Folder 488)
  - Rower, Indoor World Champion Connie Wright (YBC), Circa 1990s (Box 6, Folder 489)
  - Scenics
    - Statues: Nathan Hale, Circa 1990s (Box 6, Folder 490 - 491)
      - Plaster casting, 1986 June (Box 6, Folder 492)
    - Sterling Memorial Library, Circa 1990s (Box 6, Folder 493)
    - Windows, Circa 1990s (Box 6, Folder 494)
    - Winter [mm 428], 1997 January (Box 6, Folder 495)
    - Fall [mm 349], 1995 (Box 6, Folder 496)
    - [mm 285], 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 497)
    - [mm 380], 1996 April (Box 6, Folder 498)
    - Buildings: Renovations Brochure Secretary's office, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 499)
    - Leaf Blower: C. DeMartin, 1998 Fall (Box 6, Folder 500)
    - Buildings [mm 318], Fall 1994 (Box 6, Folder 501)
    - Stairs
      - [mm 492], 1933 May 23 (Box 6, Folder 502)
      - [mm 400], 1996 May (Box 6, Folder 503)
    - [mm 18], 1993 April 1 (Box 6, Folder 504)
    - Winter
      - [mm 79], 1994 February (Box 6, Folder 505)
      - [mm 353], 1996 January (Box 6, Folder 506)
      - [mm], 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 507)
    - Miscellaneous, Circa 1990s (Box 6, Folder 508)
    - Students miscellaneous, Circa 1990s (Box 6, Folder 509)
    - Visitors miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 510)
    - Spring 1994 [mm 87], 1994 March (Box 6, Folder 511)
    - Students
      - Spring, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 512)
      - [mm 369], 1996 March (Box 6, Folder 513)
    - Windows
      - [mm 442], 1996 September (Box 6, Folder 514)
      - [mm 361], 1995 May 19 (Box 6, Folder 515)
    - Statues, Prints, Windows [mm 36], 1993 September 16 (Box 6, Folder 516)
    - Stonework, Windows, Gateways, Archways [mm 120], 1992 December 16 (Box 6, Folder 517)
    - Fish on Cross Campus [mm 414], 1996 October 14 (Box 6, Folder 518)
    - Fog [mm 358], 1996 January (Box 6, Folder 519)
    - Holiday [mm 354], 1995 Dec, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 520)
    - New Haven, Circa 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 521 - 522)
  - Howard Safir, New York City Police Commissioner With Professor D. Rae, 2000 January (Box 6, Folder 523)
  - St. Mary's Fire [mm 514], 1998 March (Box 6, Folder 524)
  - St. Nick Play at Beinecke Lobby, Circa 1990s (Box 6, Folder 525)
  - St. Thomas More Chapel 60th anniversary, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 526)
  - Science Education Outreach Program, 1998 December (Box 6, Folder 527)
  - Science Fair [mm 368], 1996 March 12 (Box 6, Folder 528)
  - Science Fair [mm 435], 1997 March 17 (Box 6, Folder 529)
  - Science Fair in Commons, Spring 1999 (Box 6, Folder 530)
  - Science Park, Circa 1990s (Box 6, Folder 531)
  - Science Van [mm 294], 1995 April 20 (Box 6, Folder 532)
  - San Jose Taiko Drum Troupe [mm 490], 1997 October 30 (Box 6, Folder 533)
  - Saybrook College, 2000 February 16 (Box 6, Folder 534)
  - Saybrook College [mm 493], 1997 December (Box 6, Folder 535)
  - School of the 21st Century [mm 372], 1996 April (Box 6, Folder 536)
  - Sculpture Class [mm 443], 1997 April 8 (Box 7, Folder 537)
  - Security Supplement [mm 81], 1993 February (Box 7, Folder 538)
  - "Seeds of Prevention" [mm 385], 1996 April 15 (Box 7, Folder 539)
  - Senate Field Hearing with Senator Christopher Dodd [mm 111], 1992 September 3 (Box 7, Folder 540)
  - 2001 September 11 (Box 7, Folder 541)
  - Set for "ACure at Troy" [mm 516], 1998 March (Box 7, Folder 542)
  - Shalala Visit, 1999 October (Box 7, Folder 543)
  - Shafer Scholars [mm 2], 1992 July 17 (Box 7, Folder 544)
  - Shafer Scholars: Summer [mm 216], 1994 August 11 (Box 7, Folder 545)
  - Shelving Facility (Sterling Memorial Library), 2000 (Box 7, Folder 546)